Lucy Kroll Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Client File, 1916-1998 (Box 1-736)
  - Weaver, Fritz (Box 706)
    - The Cook, 1966-1969, undated
    - Counter-Espionage, 1963, undated
    - The Creation of the World and Other Business, 1971, undated
    - Creepshow, 1981-1982, undated
    - The Crimson Curtain, 1955, undated
    - Cry for All of Us, 1970, undated
    - Curtains! 1976, undated
    - David Copperfield, 1980, undated
    - “David Frost Show,” 1970-1971
    - The Day of the Dolphin, 1972-1973, undated
    - Days of Heaven, 1976
    - The Dead Poets Society, 1988, undated
    - Death of a Ghost, 1961
    - Deathtrap, 1978-1979
    - Defend to the Death, 1980, undated
    - “The Defenders” (Box 711)
      - “Medal for a Turned Coat,” 1963-1964, undated
      - “The Riot,” 1961-1962
      - “The Traitor,” 1962-1963
    - Demon Seed, 1976-1977, 1986, undated
    - Design for Living, 1971
    - The Devil Makes Sunday, 1960-1961
    - The Devil's Advocate, 1960, undated
    - Dialogue for Lovers, 1980-1981, undated
    - “Dick Cavett Show,” 1972
    - “Dr. Kildare,” 1962-1963, undated
    - The Doctor's Dilemma, 1954-1955
    - Dog Day Afternoon, 1974, undated
    - A Doll's House, 1970-1975, undated
    - The Downside Risk, 1989
    - Dream West, 1985-1986
    - The Dresser, 1980-1982, undated
    - Drinks Before Dinner, 1978, undated
    - The Drowning Pool, 1974
    - The Duchess and the Smug, 1962, undated
    - “Dupont Show of the Month”
      - The Night of the Storm, 1961, undated
      - A Tale of Two Cities, 1958, undated
    - “Earplay,” “The 75th,” 1978, undated
    - Edge of Survival, 1980-1981, undated
    - Edith Stein, 1969, undated
    - 84 Charing Cross Road, 1982, undated
    - Eliot, T. S., poetry reading, 1988
    - Eminent Domain, 1978-1980, 1987
    - “The Endless Journey,” 1982, undated
    - Endless Love, 1980, undated
    - “An Enemy of the People,” 1966, 1985
    - “The Equalizer,” 1986-1988, undated
    - Equitable Life Assurance Society of the United States, 1986, undated
    - Equus, 1976-1977, undated
    - Escape from Rat Hell, 1964, undated
    - “The Eternal Light,” 1957-1961, undated
    - The European, 1976, undated
    - Every Good Boy Deserves a Favor, 1978, undated
    - Everybody Wants a Happy Ending, 1967
    - Evita, 1979, undated
    - “Eye on New York,” 1965-1970, undated
    - The Fabulous Dr. Fable, 1972
    - Fail Safe, 1963-1964, undated
    - Falstaff, 1966, undated
    - Family Reunion, 1958, undated
    - Faust, 1982, undated
    - “The F.B.I.,” 1965-1971, undated
    - “Felony Squad,” “Conspiracy of Power,” 1968, undated (Box 712)
    - “Fields of Glory,” “The Historic Battlefields of America,” 1994
    - Flint, 1970-1973
    - Floating Dragon, 1986-1988
    - The Formula, 1979, undated
    - The Freebooters, 1966-1967, undated
    - “From Sea to Shining Sea,” “Give Me Liberty,” 1974, undated
    - “The Fugitive,” 1965-1966, undated
    - Funny Lady, 1974
    - “Gentle Ben,” “Take a Giant Step,” 1967, undated
    - The Ginger Man, 1959
    - “The Good Lieutenant,” 1966, undated
    - The Great Adventure, 1966
    - The Great God Brown, 1959, undated
    - The Greatest Story Ever Told, 1962
    - Group 20 Players, 1955-1957
    - “Guns of August,” 1964
    - “Gunsmoke,” “Old Friend,” 1966, undated
    - Habeas Corpus, 1975, undated
    - “Hallmark Theatre,” “Small Miracles,” 1972
    - Hamlet, 1956-1964, 1980, undated, (2 folders)
    - Have a Nice Weekend, 1972, undated
    - “Hawaii Five-0,” 1978-1979
    - Heartbreak House, 1959, undated
    - Heaven with a Gun, 1968
    - Henry IV, 1960, undated
    - “History of Television,” 1985
    - Hogan's Goat, 1969, undated
    - Holocaust
      - Contracts, 1977
      - Correspondence, 1977-1979, 1987-1989, undated
      - Financial records, 1977
      - Miscellany, undated
      - Notes, 1977-1979, undated
      - Photographs, undated
      - Printed matter, 1977-1979, undated (Box 713)
    - Horror File, 1986, undated
    - “The Hunter,” 1969-1970
    - Hurrah, Boys, Hurrah! 1968
    - I Remember Mama, 1978-1979, undated
    - I Shall Return, 1976
    - I'll Take Manhattan, 1986, undated
    - In Cold Blood, 1966, undated
    - Incident, 1970, undated
    - The Infinite Voyage, 1987-1989, undated
    - Inner Voices, 1986, undated
    - International Monitor Awards, International Teleproduction Society, 1994
    - International Poetry Forum, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1975
    - The Interns, 1961
    - “The Invaders,” 1967-1968
    - Ironclads, 1990, undated
    - “I've Got a Secret,” 1965
    - Jacobs, Michael, project, 1994
    - Jane Eyre, 1961, undated
    - John and Abigail, 1970, undated
    - The Jolly Corner, 1975-1985, undated
    - Joy in the Morning, 1964
    - Julius Caesar, 1955-1961, 1979, 1987, undated
    - Jumpers, 1973
    - “Kent State,” 1980, undated
    - “Kentucky Ride,” 1979, undated
    - Kenya, 1988
    - King Cobra, 1980-1981, undated
    - King John, 1956, undated
    - King Lear
      - Contracts, 1991
      - Correspondence, 1982, 1991 (Box 714)
      - Financial records, 1991
      - Miscellany, 1991, undated
      - Photograph, 1991
      - Printed matter, 1991
    - King's Ransom, 1986, undated
    - “Kojak,” 1976-1977, undated
    - “Kraft Television Theatre,” 1955
    - “Kung Fu,” 1974, 1980
    - La Cage Aux Folles, 1982, undated
    - “L.A. Law,” 1976, undated
    - Labyrinth, 1956, undated
    - Lady in a Cage, 1963, undated
    - The Lathe of Heaven, 1978-1979
    - “Law and Order,” 1991-1992
    - The Legend of Lizzie Borden, 1974-1975, undated
    - L'Histoire du Soldat, 1954-1959, 1983, undated
    - Life With Father, 1974-1976, 1982, undated
    - Light Up the Sky, 1987, undated
    - Lincoln, 1976, undated
    - Lincoln-Douglas Debates, 1963, 1981-1986
    - The Lion in Winter, 1968, 1977, undated
    - Little Big Man, 1969, undated
    - Little Foxes, 1981, undated
    - Long Day's Journey Into Night, 1969, 1974-1975, undated
    - Lorenzo, 1962-1963, undated See also Oversize
    - MacArthur
      - Correspondence, 1973-1976, undated
      - Notes, 1973-1976, undated (Box 715)
      - Printed matter, 1973-1976, undated
    - Macbeth, 1972-1973, undated
    - “Maid in America,” 1982-1983, undated
    - Major Barbara, 1976-1979, undated
    - The Maltese Bippy, 1967-1969, undated
    - Man and Superman, 1977-1978, undated
    - A Man For All Seasons, 1960, 1968, undated
    - Man From a Missing Country, 1971
    - “The Man From U.N.C.L.E.,” 1963-1965, undated
    - Man of La Mancha, 1962-1970, undated
    - “Mancusco,” 1990
    - “Mannix,” “Edge of the Knife,” 1968-1972
    - Marathon Man, 1975, 1987, undated
    - “The Martian Chronicles,” 1978-1980, undated
    - The Martyrdom of St. Sebastian, 1962-1966, undated
    - The Master Builder, 1954-1955, 1977-1978, undated
    - Meanwhile Back at the Front, 1966-1967
    - “Medicine in America,” 1985
    - “The Medics,” 1971-1972, undated
    - “The Middle Ages,” 1984, undated
    - A Midsummer Night's Dream, 1978, 1986, undated
    - “Millennium: 1000 Years of Music,” 1985-1986, undated
    - The Misanthrope, 1973, undated
    - Miscellany
      - Agents
        - Blake-Glenn Agency, Ltd., 1974-1983, undated
        - Camden Artists, Ltd., 1987-1989, undated (Box 716)
        - Doyle, Dane, Bernbach, Inc. Advertising, 1968-1970
        - Jack Fields Associates, 1983-1984, undated
        - Kumin-Olenick Agency, 1961, 1972-1975
        - Michael Thomas Agency, 1972-1991, undated
        - Progressive Artists Agency, 1976-1979, undated
        - Ted Bates and Co., 1970-1972
        - Thomas Craven Films, 1972-1974, undated
        - Warwick and Legler, 1970-1972
        - Young and Rubicam, 1967, undated
      - Biographical material, 1955-1979, undated
      - Casting calls, 1986-1992
      - Contracts, 1954-1989, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
        - 1953-1961, (2 folders)
        - 1962-1994, undated, (7 folders) (Box 717)
      - Financial records, 1959-1991, undated, (2 folders)
      - Notes (Box 718)
        - 1955-1984, (6 folders)
        - 1985-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 719)
      - Photographs, undated
      - Printed matter, 1955-1993, undated
    - Miss Lonelyhearts, 1956-1957, undated
    - “Mission Impossible”
      - “The Charity,” 1967
      - “Illusion,” 1969
      - “Operation Rogosh,” 1966-1967, undated
    - “Momma,” “Death and Taxes,” 1979, undated
    - Monsieur Amilcar, 1979, undated
    - Morning, Noon, and Night, 1968
    - Mourning Becomes Electra, 1978, undated
    - Motive, 1971, 1978, undated
    - Much Ado About Nothing, 1959, 1969, undated
    - “Murder, She Wrote,” 1986-1988, undated
    - Murderous Angels, 1971
    - My Fair Lady, 1964-1968, 1975, undated
    - My Name Is Bill W., 1989, undated
    - “My New York,” “Walt Whitman and Friends,” 1983
    - The Naked Truth, 1961, undated
    - “The Name of the Game,” “The Inquiry,” 1968
    - Network, 1975, undated
    - “Never Too Late,” 1975-1976, undated
    - “New Breed,” 1961, undated
    - Night Life, 1962, undated
    - Nightwings, 1986-1988
    - “Norman's Corner,” 1988, undated
    - “The Nurses,” “Seeing Heart,” 1962-1964
    - “N.Y.P.D.,” “Nothing Is Real But the Dead,” 1968-1971
    - “Old Money,” 1988, undated
    - Old Times, 1972
    - “Omnibus,” “Moment of Truth,” 1957-1958, undated
    - Once There Was a Russian, 1956, undated
    - The One-Eyed Cat See Container 720, Phantom Gold
    - “One Life to Live,” 1988-1989, undated
    - Other Voices, Other Rooms, 1971, undated
    - Our Man Flint, 1966, undated (Box 720)
    - Our Town, 1977, 1987
    - “Out of Dust,” 1959
    - “The Outcasts”
      - “Butcher of Bemington,” 1968, undated
      - “Take Your Lover in the Ring,” 1968
    - Over My Dead Body, 1984, undated
    - Overnight, 1971
    - The Parallax View, 1973, undated
    - Patrick's Day, 1972, undated
    - Peer Gynt, 1956-1960, undated
    - Pendulum, 1968, undated
    - “The Pennsylvania History Series,” “The Pennsylvania Experiment,” 1980, undated
    - Perched on a Gabardine Cloud, 1979, undated
    - Phantom Gold, 1989-1990, undated
    - Phoenix Theatre, New York, N.Y., 1958-1960, undated
    - “The Play of the Week,” “The Potting Shed,” 1960-1961, undated
    - “Playhouse 90,” “Out of Dust,” 1959, undated
    - The Play's the Thing, 1975-1981, undated
    - Pollyanna, 1959, undated
    - Poor Murderer, 1976
    - Portrait of Raoul Wallenberg, 1990, undated
    - “Power,” 1988, undated
    - The Power and the Glory, 1958-1962, undated
    - Prelude to a Kiss, 1987-1990
    - Present Laughter, 1974, undated
    - “Preston Sturges: The Rise and Fall of an American Dreamer,”
      - 1989-1990, undated
    - The Price, 1979-1986, undated
    - Prometheus Bound, 1972, undated
    - Protective Custody, 1956-1957, undated
    - “The Pursuers” See Container 713, “The Hunter”
    - Pygmalion, 1968-1971, undated
    - “The Questions,” 1967, undated
    - Rag Dolly, 1980, 1986, undated
    - “Rawhide,” 1964-1965, undated
    - “Romeo and Juliet in Kansas City,” 1975
    - Romulus, 1961, undated (Box 721)
    - The Rothschilds, 1969-1970, undated
    - The Ruling Class, 1970
    - “Rx for the Defense,” 1971-1972, undated
    - “A Salute to the American Theatre,” 1959-1960
    - The Crucible, 1959, 1966-1972, 1991-1992, undated
    - San Diego Trust and Savings Bank, San Diego, Calif., 1981-1982, undated
    - Savages, 1974, undated
    - “The Scarlet Letter,” 1977-1978, undated
    - Scenes from a Marriage, 1974
    - Scotts on the Rocks, 1975, undated
    - “Search for Tomorrow,” 1985-1986, undated
    - Sergeant Steiner, 1962
    - Serjeant Musgrave's Dance, 1965, undated
    - “Sesame Street,” 1983-1987, undated
    - “Seven Who Were Hanged,” 1960, undated
    - Shadowlands, 1990, undated
    - “Shamus,” 1972
    - Sherlock Holmes, 1975
    - “Shock-A-Bye, Baby,” 1973, undated
    - A Shot in the Dark, 1962, undated
    - 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue, 1975, undated
    - The Skin of Our Teeth, 1960, 1967, undated
    - “Skywatchers,” 1989
    - Sleeping Prince, 1956, undated
    - The Soldier's Tale See Container 714, L'Histoire du Soldat
    - The Sorrows of Frederick
      - Contracts, 1967
      - Correspondence, 1966-1971, undated
      - Financial records, 1967, undated
      - Miscellany, 1967, undated
      - Notes, 1966-1974, undated
      - Printed matter, 1967
    - Speed Is of the Essence, 1970
    - “The Spirit of Pittsburgh,” 1988, undated
    - The Sponsor, 1972-1973
    - The Staircase, 1969
    - “Studio One,” “The Playwright and the Star,” 1957, undated
    - The Sudden and Accidental Re-Education of Horse Johnson
      - 1966-1968, undated
    - Sullivan and Gilbert
      - Contracts, 1988, undated
      - Correspondence, 1988, undated
      - Financial records, 1988, undated (Box 722)
      - Miscellany, 1988
      - Notes, 1988, undated
      - Printed matter, 1988
    - A Tale Told
      - Contracts, 1981
      - Correspondence, 1981, undated
      - Notes, 1981, undated
      - Printed matter, 1981, undated
    - “Tales from the Dark Side,” 1981-1985, undated
    - Tales of Poe, 1986-1988
    - The Taming of the Shrew, 1956, undated
    - Tartuffe, 1967, 1976, 1982, undated
    - Tattered Tom, 1969
    - The Tell Tale Heart, 1963
    - The Tempest, 1955, 1969, 1977-1981, undated
    - Ten: The Musical, 1984, undated
    - “Texas,” 1980, undated
    - The Three Little Pigs, 1990
    - “To Tell the Truth,” 1965
    - Tobacco Row, 1974
    - A Touch of the Poet, 1973-1974, undated
    - Twelfth Night, 1959, undated
    - Twelve Caesars, 1992-1993, undated
    - “Twelve O'clock High,” 1964
    - “The Twilight Zone”
      - Miscellany, 1966, 1977
      - “Obsolete Man,” 1961, undated
      - “Third from the Sun,” 1959-1960, undated
    - Undiscovered Country, 1980 (Box 723)
    - “United States Steel Hour”
      - “The Imposter,” 1960, undated
      - “Little Tin God,” 1959-1962, undated
      - Miscellany, 1958-1962
    - “The Untouchables,” 1960-1961
    - “Vision USA,” 1971-1972, undated
    - Wages of Sin, 1972, undated
    - A Walk in the Spring Rain, 1969-1970, undated
    - “Walt Disney Presents,” 1966
    - The Way of the World, 1954, undated
    - “Way Out,” 1961, undated
    - “We the People,” 1987, undated
    - “Weather Report 80,” “The Almost, Not Quite, Sure Thing,”
      - 1979-1980, undated
    - When We Dead Awaken, 1976, 1990-1991
    - The White Devil, 1955-1960, undated
    - The White House, 1961-1967, undated
    - Whose Life Is It Anyway? 1959, undated
    - Why Hitler Lost the War, 1988-1989, undated
    - “Wonder Woman,” 1977-1978, undated
    - “Woodrow and Edith Wilson,” 1975, undated
    - Woody Allen Fall Project 1990, 1990-1991, undated
    - The World of Carl Sandburg, 1966-1967
    - Wrong Turn at Lungfish, 1990-1993, undated
    - “You Are There,” “Columbus and Isabella,” 1971
    - You Can't Go Home Again, 1978
    - Zabriski Point, 1968, undated
  - Weaver, Lydia, 1980-1985, undated
  - Webb, Katherine, 1971
  - Weil, Suzanne, 1985-1989
  - Weinreb, Nathaniel Norsen
    - The Babylonians, 1953, undated
    - Contracts, 1955-1956
    - The Copper Scrolls, 1946, 1956-1960, undated (Box 724)
    - Correspondence, 1955-1959
    - Esther, 1955
    - The Frozen Flame, 1959, undated
    - Notes, 1954-1958, undated
    - The Shooter, 1955
    - The Sorceress, 1954
  - Weinstein, Henry
    - Contracts, 1954
    - Correspondence, 1953-1962, (2 folders)
    - Notes and printed matter, 1953-1961, undated
  - Weisman, John
    - Evidence
      - Contracts, 1978
      - Correspondence, 1976-1983, (2 folders)
      - Financial records, 1980-1985
      - Galley proofs, undated
      - Notes, 1977-1981, undated
      - Printed matter, 1980, undated
    - Hostage in the Oval Office, 1975, undated (Box 725)
    - Miscellany
      - Correspondence, 1977-1981
      - Notes, 1979-1980, undated
      - Printed matter, 1974-1981, undated
    - Watchdogs, 1979-1984, undated
  - Weiss, Louise, 1968
  - Weissman, Michaele
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980, undated
    - Notes and printed matter, 1979-1980, undated
    - Typescripts, 1978-1980, undated, (2 folders)
  - Welch, Mary
    - Contracts, 1951-1957, undated
    - Correspondence
      - 1951-1954, (4 folders)
      - 1956-1958, undated (Box 726)
    - Notes, 1951-1958, undated
    - Printed matter, 1952-1958, undated
  - Wells, Malcolm See Container 30, Bloomgarden, Henry S.
  - Wells, Rebecca
    - Gloria Duplex
      - Contracts, 1988, undated
      - Correspondence, 1987-1989, (2 folders)
      - Notes, 1987-1989, undated, (2 folders)
      - Photographs, undated
      - Printed matter, 1987
      - Script, 1987
    - Miscellany
      - Contracts, 1987
      - Correspondence, 1986-1989, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1987-1989, undated (Box 727)
      - Photographs, undated
    - National Artists Management Co., 1988, undated
    - Splittin' Hairs
      - Contracts, 1988
      - Correspondence, 1987-1989
      - Notes and printed matter, 1984-1989, undated, (2 folders)
  - West, Cheryl
    - Contracts, 1989-1992
    - Correspondence, 1992-1995
    - Notes and printed matter, 1991-1995, undated
    - Script, 1989
  - Wheeler, Billy Edd
    - Contracts and correspondence, 1962-1968
    - Fire on the Mountain, 1965
    - Hatfields and McCoys, 1970, undated (Box 728)
    - New York Folk Festival, New York, N.Y., 1965, undated
    - Notes, 1962-1964, undated
    - Phonograph record, 1962
    - Photographs, 1964-1965
    - Printed matter, 1963-1968, undated
    - Slatefall, 1962-1965, undated
    - War in Appalachia, 1966-1967
  - Wheeler, Timothy, 1989-1990, undated
  - Whipple, Chandler, 1967
  - Whitcraft, Melissa
    - Correspondence, 1977-1981, undated, (2 folders)
    - Notes, 1977-1980, undated
    - Printed matter, 1979, undated
  - White, Charles, 1983-1989, undated
  - White, Jane, 1952-1953, undated
  - White, John F., 1978
  - Whitney, Helen, 1978, 1986-1987
  - Whyte, Ron
    - The Ballad of Emil and Nell, 1976-1977, undated
    - Castaways, 1976-1977, undated (Box 729)
    - A Connecticut Yankee in King Arthur's Court, 1975
    - Correspondence, 1975-1977, 1983-1990, (3 folders)
    - The Extinction of Alexander Pope, 1975-1977, undated
    - Funeral March for a One Man Band, 1968-1977
    - Horatio, 1974-1977
    - Life Deformed, 1976, undated
    - Notes and printed matter, 1972-1984, undated
    - Photograph, undated
    - Radio City Music Hall project, 1975-1977, undated
  - Wilbur, Cornelia (Box 730)
    - Contracts, 1964, 1984, undated
    - Correspondence, 1984-1985, (2 folders)
    - Notes and printed matter, 1984-1986, undated
    - Typescripts, undated
  - Willard, Katherine, 1960, undated
  - Williams, Barbara
    - Contracts, 1957-1961, 1985
    - Correspondence, 1958-1961, 1985-1986
    - Notes, 1960-1972, 1985-1987, undated
    - Photographs, undated
    - Printed matter, 1960-1962, 1971, 1985-1986, undated
    - Submissions, 1986-1987
  - Williams, Elizabeth, 1968-1974, undated
  - Williams, George Llyonel, 1951-1952
  - Williams, J. Richard, 1982-1983
  - Williams, Joan (Box 731)
    - Contracts, 1960-1961, 1970, 1983
    - Correspondence, 1968-1976, undated, (2 folders)
    - Notes, 1969-1973, undated
    - Printed matter, 1961-1962, 1971, undated
    - Royalty statements, 1970-1982
    - Typescript, 1971
  - Williams, John A., 1988-1989
  - Williams, William W., 1983
  - Wilson, Francis
    - Contracts, 1966-1968
    - Correspondence, 1966-1973
    - Notes, 1966-1968
    - Royalty statements, 1968-1972
  - Wilson, Scott, 1985-1986
  - Winer, Stephen See Container 686, Tiedemann, Karl (Box 732)
  - Winiewicz, Lida, 1970-1971
  - Winters, Jonathan, 1952-1954, undated
  - Winters, Marian, and Wilbur Pippin
    - Contracts, 1978
    - Correspondence, 1978-1982, 1991
    - Notes, 1978-1980, undated
    - Printed matter, 1978-1979, undated
    - Royalty statements, 1979-1985
  - Winters, Olga See Containers 19-20, Bellin, Olga
  - Wisniewski, Edward J., 1984 See also Container 328, Janusz, Edward W.
  - Withington, Virginia, 1979-1980
  - Wittenberg, Rudolph, 1976-1981, undated
  - Wolfkill, Grant, and Jerry A. Rose See also Container 591, Rose, Jerry A.
    - Contracts, 1965
    - Correspondence
      - 1963-1964, (3 folders)
      - 1965-1969, undated, (4 folders) (Box 733)
    - Drawings, undated
    - Financial records, 1965-1969, undated
    - Notes, 1963-1967, undated
    - Photographs, 1962-1964, undated
    - Printed matter, 1961-1965, undated
    - Typescript, 1964
  - Wood, Bradford, and Gregory A. Poplyk (Box 734)
    - Contracts and correspondence, 1990-1991, undated
    - Notes and printed matter, 1990-1991, undated
    - Royalty statements, 1990-1991
  - Wood, Christopher, 1973-1980, undated
  - Wood, John, 1985-1987, undated
  - Worden, Helen
    - The Brief Hour of François Villon, 1965-1966, undated
    - Miscellany, 1953, 1965-1966, 1977-1978, undated
    - The Private Life of Helen of Troy
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966, 1977-1979, undated
      - Notes and printed matter, 1966, 1977-1978, undated
      - Script, 1977, undated
    - The Turbulent Story of Cellular Therapy and Dr. Niehans
      - Correspondence, 1964-1966
      - Miscellany, 1965-1966, undated
    - The Widow Who Wouldn't, 1978, undated
  - Wurdemann, Audrey May, 1960 (Box 735)
  - Wurman, Richard Saul, 1979, undated
  - Wymark, Olwen
    - Correspondence, 1965-1969, undated
    - Miscellany, 1967-1968, undated
  - Yamada, Eimi, 1987, undated
  - Yates, Ted
    - Correspondence, 1959-1967
    - Miscellany, 1960-1967, undated
  - Yeomans, John, 1949
  - Young, Gig, 1951-1960, undated
  - Youngblood, Shay, 1991
  - Yuriko See Container 427, Kikuchi, Yuriko
  - Zaret, Hy, and Lou Singer, 1945-1951, 1961-1962, undated (Box 736)
  - Zeman, Thomas, 1988-1989
  - Zito, Penny K., 1985-1986
- Miscellany, 1908-1997 (Box 736-758)
  Address books, awards, correspondence between family members and friends, personal financial records, notes, photographs, printed material, and scripts.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material and chronologically therein.
  - Family papers (Box 736)
    - Address and memoranda books, 1973-1985, undated, (5 folders)
    - Artwork, 1975-1977, undated
    - Awards (Box 737)
      - Living Legacy Award
        - 10th annual, 1991-1994, undated, (3 folders)
        - 11th annual, 1992-1994, undated
        - 12th annual, 1994
        - 13th annual, 1995-1996, undated
      - Other awards, 1985, 1994
    - Biographical material, 1940-1945, 1984-1985, 1992-1997, undated
    - Charitable work and contributions, 1970-1972, 1980, undated
    - Correspondence
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1945-1948, 1962, 1973, 1987, undated
      - Bochco, Mimi and Steven, 1964, 1976-1996, undated
      - Bocour, Leonard, 1987, undated (Box 738)
      - Bradley, Elizabeth, 1989, 1995
      - Browne, Sandra, 1979, undated
      - Buchwald, Mary and Ronald, 1947-1948, 1968, 1981-1984, undated
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1947-1964, 1976
      - Central Hudson Gas and Electric Co., 1948
      - Chapin, Schuyler G., 1976-1978, undated
      - “C” miscellaneous, 1947-1949, 1962-1967, 1982-1986
      - Davidson, Joan, 1987, undated
      - Derman family, 1952-1962
      - “D” miscellaneous, 1960-1965, 1980-1986, undated
      - “E” miscellaneous, 1947, 1975, 1990
      - Felton, Norman, 1983
      - “F-G” miscellaneous, 1947-1952, 1965-1980, 1990
      - Hall, Marie C., 1984-1987
      - Hanes, R. Philip, Jr., 1986, 1994, undated
      - Harding, Joshua, 1964-1966, undated
      - Harding, Sarah, 1992-1996, undated
      - Harris, Julie, 1959, 1994
      - Hendricks, Delmar, 1986
      - Herman, Stephanie, 1975-1979, undated
      - “H” miscellaneous, 1963, 1976-1994
      - Jaffe family, 1947-1948, 1990
      - “J” miscellaneous, 1947-1948, 1956, 1980
      - Kaplan, Harriet, 1947-1948
      - Kinsella, Marian, 1964-1965